Preliminary Inventory to the International Rescue Committee Records, 1946-1989
Hoover Institution Archives
International Rescue Committee Records,
1946-1989
82033
International Rescue Committee
3802 manuscript boxes (1585.5 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Case files, correspondence, reports, memoranda, financial records, personnel records, and statistics, relating to resettlement of refugees and displaced persons, and especially to refugees from Europe after World War II, from the post-World War II communist countries of Eastern Europe, from Hungary after the Hungarian Revolution of 1956, from Cuba after the Cuban Revolution of 1959, and from Indochina after the end of the Vietnamese War in 1975.
Administrative Information
Access
Users must sign a use agreement for access to the collection. Boxes 2400-2405 may not be used without written permission of the International Rescue Committee.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Access Points
International relief.; Refugees.; World War, 1939-1945.; World War, 1939-1945--Refugees.; Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975--Refugees.; Cuba--History--Revolution, 1959.; Europe.; Hungary.; Hungary--History--Revolution, 1956.; Europe, Eastern.; Cuba.; Indochina.; Vietnam.; Laos.; Cambodia.
Container List
- Miscellaneous reports, personnel records, correspondence, and statistics, ca. 1960-1973 (Box 132-135)
- Field correspondence files, 1961 (Box 302-307)
- Alphabetic files, 1961 (Box 458-462)
- Administrative files, 1961-1964 (Box 1197-1201)
- Administrative files, Financial files, 1961-1964 (Box 1206-1210)
- Administrative files, Miscellany, 1961-1964 (Box 1210-1213)
- Alphabetic files, 1961-1964 (Box 1202-1206)
- Field correspondence files, 1962 (Box 442-447)
- Alphabetic files, 1962 (Box 447-452)
- Alphabetic files, 1962-1963 (Box 453-457)
- Field correspondence files, 1963 (Box 393-397)
- Alphabetic files, 1963 (Box 398-402)
- Field correspondence files, 1964 (Box 297-302)
- Alphabetic files, 1964 (Box 388-392)
- Field correspondence files, 1965 (Box 291-296)
- Alphabetic files, 1965 (Box 286-291)
- Alphabetic files, 1965-1975
  - B-C (Box 1187-1191)
  - C-I (Box 1191-1196)
  - I-R (Box 1175-1180)
  - R-Z, Job applications (Box 1181-1186)
- Field correspondence files, 1966 (Box 1140-1144)
- Alphabetic files, 1966 (Box 1145-1150)
- Cuban program files, Miscellany, 1966 (Box 1150-1155)
- Field correspondence files, 1967 (Box 1817-1822)
- Alphabetic files, 1967 (Box 1823-1828)
- Field correspondence files, 1968 (Box 1806-1812)
- Alphabetic files, 1968 (Box 1812-1817)
- Field correspondence files, 1969 (Box 321-326)
- Alphabetic files, 1969 (Box 317-321)
- Field correspondence files, 1970 (Box 307-312)
- Alphabetic files, 1970 (Box 312-316)
- Field correspondence files, 1971 (Box 1795-1800)
- Alphabetic files, 1971 (Box 1800-1806)
- Field correspondence files, 1972 (Box 1784-1789)
- Alphabetic files, 1972 (Box 1789-1794)
- Field correspondence files, Cuban program files, Intergovernmental Committee for European Migration files, Job applications, 1973 (Box 672-676)
- Alphabetic files, 1973 (Box 677-682)
- Field correspondence files, American Council on Judaism files, Cuban program files, Intergovernmental Committee for European Migration files, 1974 (Box 662-666)
- Alphabetic files, 1974 (Box 667-672)
- Field correspondence files, 1975 (Box 1724-1727)
- Alphabetic files, 1975 (Box 1728-1732)
- Indochina program files, 1975 (Box 1733-1738)
- Field correspondence files, 1976 (Box 847-849)
- Alphabetic files, 1976 (Box 849-854)
- Regional office files, Indochina program files, 1976 (Box 855-859)
- Indochina program files, Job applications, Miscellany, 1976 (Box 859-862)
- Field office files, 1977 (Box 216-220)
- Alphabetic files, 1977 (Box 221-226)
- Indochina program files, 1977 (Box 227-230)
- Field office files, 1978 (Box 272-275)
- Alphabetic files, 1978 (Box 276-280)
- Indochina program files, 1978 (Box 280-283)
- Contracts, Job applications, Chile program files, 1978 (Box 283-285)
- Chronological files, 1978 (Box 378-380)
- Citizens Commission on Indochina Refugees files, 1978-1982 (Box 1698-1701)
- Field office files, 1979 (Box 1391-1395)
- Alphabetic files, 1979
  - A-C (Box 1391-1395)
  - C-H, Contracts, Job applications (Box 1395-1400)
  - I-Z, Indochina program files (Box 1406-1411)
- Chronological files, 1979-1982 (Box 1400-1405)
- Administrative files, 1979-1985 (Box 1702-1703)
- Field office files, Contracts, 1980 (Box 230-236)
- Alphabetic files, 1980 (Box 236-242)
- Indochina program files, 1980 (Box 242-247)
- Nominal rolls, Cuban contract files, 1980 (Box 381-385)
- Overseas office files, 1980 (Box 501-510)
- Regional office files, 1980 (Box 511-515)
- Cuban contract files, 1980-1982 (Box 386-388)
- Indochina program files, 1980-1984 (Box 1685-1697)
- Field office files, U.S. refugee program files, Cuban program files, 1981 (Box 364-368)
- Alphabetic files, 1981 (Box 368-373)
- Indochina program files, 1981 (Box 374-378)
- Job applications, 1981 (Box 378-380)
- Overseas office files, 1981 (Box 1367-1372)
- Regional office files, 1981 (Box 1373-1378)
- Regional office files, 1981 (Box 516-520)
- Field office files, Contracts, 1982 (Box 485-490)
- Alphabetic files, 1982 (Box 490-495)
- Indochina program files, 1982 (Box 495-500)
- Overseas office files, 1982 (Box 179-188)
- Regional office files, 1982 (Box 189-197)
- Field office files, Central America program files, 1983 (Box 253-257)
- Alphabetic files, 1983 (Box 257-262)
- Indochina program files, 1983 (Box 263-267)
- Overseas office files, 1983 (Box 1385-1391)
- Regional office files, 1983 (Box 1378-1384)
- Chronological files, Job applications, Miscellany, 1983-1984 (Box 248-253)
- Field office files, Central America program files, 1984 (Box 1558-1563)
- Alphabetic files, 1984 (Box 340-344)
- Overseas office files, 1984 (Box 547-555)
- Regional office files, 1984 (Box 541-546)
- Regional office files, Alphabetic files, Chronological files, Job applications, 1984 (Box 823-828)
- Field office files, 1985 (Box 327-331)
- Alphabetic files, 1985 (Box 331-336)
- Alphabetic files, 1985 (Box 1233-1237)
- Regional office files, Joint Voluntary Agency files, Thailand medical program files, Job applications, 1985 (Box 336-339)
- Chronological files, 1985-1986 (Box 268-271)
- Field office files, 1986 (Box 1546-1549)
- Alphabetic files, 1986
  - A-T (Box 1549-1554)
  - T-Z, Thailand program files, Job applications (Box 1554-1558)
- Field correspondence files, 1987 (Box 809-813)
- Alphabetic files, 1987
  - A-T (Box 813-818)
  - U-Z (Box 809-813)
- Regional office files, Chronological files, Job applications, 1987 (Box 818-823)
- Field office files, 1988 (Box 1666-1670)
- Alphabetic files, 1988
  - A-S (Box 1671-1675)
  - T-Z (Box 1676-1680)
- Regional office files, 1988 (Box 1676-1680)
- Chronological files, Job applications, Miscellany, 1988 (Box 1681-1684)
- Surplus commodity (P.L. 480) files, Agency for International Development contracts, Vouchers, Procurement authorizations (Box 556-561)
- Robert De Vecchi files (Indochina program) (Box 705-729)
- Indochina program files (Box 1238-1243)
- Cuban program files (Box 1116-1118)
- Cuban ex-political prisoner files (Box 1118-1120)
- Refugee case files, 1946-1957 (mainly Eastern European, and especially Hungarian)
  - A-Bakl (Box 1-5)
  - Bako-Biele (Box 6-10)
  - Bieli-Bui (Box 11-15)
  - Buj-Debrec (Box 16-20)
  - Debres-Ench (Box 21-25)
  - Encs-Fran (Box 26-30)
  - Frat-Gord (Box 31-35)
  - Gore-Haue (Box 36-40)
  - Haus-Hube (Box 41-45)
  - Hubr-Jup (Box 46-50)
  - Jur-Keresztes, I. (Box 51-55)
  - Keresztes, T.-Konk (Box 56-60)
  - Konr-Lach (Box 61-65)
  - Lacz-Lovasz, A. (Box 66-70)
  - Lovasz, G.-Mele (Box 71-75)
  - Meli-Nagy, Miklos (Box 76-80)
  - Nagy, Miklos-Pasi (Box 81-85)
  - Pask-Rab (Box 86-90)
  - Rac-Sallai (Box 91-95)
  - Sallay-Silli (Box 96-100)
  - Silly-Stej (Box 101-105)
  - Stek-Szilly, L. (Box 106-110)
  - Szilly, M.-Tschapka (Box 111-115)
  - Tschapka-Ve (Box 116-120)
  - Vi-Wl (Box 121-125)
  - Wn-Z (Box 126-131)
- Refugee case files (mainly Eastern European)
  - A-Antol (Box 750-754)
  - Anton-Balaj (Box 754-759)
  - Balan-Beca (Box 759-764)
  - Bech-Bey (Box 764-769)
  - Bez-Bog (Box 1472-1476)
  - Boh-Br (Box 1477-1481)
  - Bu-Cap (Box 1482-1486)
  - Car-Cin (Box 1486-1491)
  - Cio-Cub (Box 1646-1651)
  - Cuc-Deka (Box 1651-1656)
  - Dekk-Det (Box 1656-1661)
  - Dev-Do (Box 1625-1630)
  - Dr-El (Box 1630-1635)
  - Em-Fisc (Box 1636-1641)
  - Fise-Gari (Box 1641-1646)
  - Garn-Gla (Box 1605-1610)
  - Gli-Gun (Box 1610-1615)
  - Gur-Hl (Box 1615-1619)
  - Ho-Ibrahim (Box 1620-1624)
  - Ibrahimi-Iv (Box 403-407)
  - Iw-Jovanov (Box 407-412)
  - Jovanovi-Kam (Box 412-416)
  - Kan-Kira (Box 416-421)
  - Kirc-Kono (Box 957-961)
  - Konr-Kowalc (Box 961-966)
  - Kowale-Krul (Box 966-971)
  - Krum-Lal (Box 971-976)
  - Lam-Lim (Box 899-903)
  - Lin-Mach (Box 904-908)
  - Macik-Marik (Box 909-913)
  - Marin-Meh (Box 914-918)
  - Mei-Mil (Box 880-884)
  - Min-Mon (Box 885-889)
  - Moo-Nac (Box 889-894)
  - Nad-Nig (Box 894-898)
  - Nik-Ok (Box 992-996)
  - Ol-Palo (Box 996-1001)
  - Palt-Pere (Box 1001-1006)
  - Perh-Pl (Box 1006-1010)
  - Po-Puj (Box 344-349)
  - Pur-Rim (Box 349-354)
  - Rin-Sale (Box 354-358)
  - Sali-Sel (Box 359-363)
  - Sem-Sim (Box 938-942)
  - Sin-Spe (Box 942-947)
  - Spi-Stojan (Box 947-951)
  - Stojano-Svi (Box 952-956)
  - Svo-Szw (Box 919-923)
  - Szy-Ti (Box 923-928)
  - Tj-Trun (Box 928-933)
  - Trup-Val (Box 933-938)
  - Vam-Verl (Box 1704-1709)
  - Vern-Vuk (Box 1709-1714)
  - Vul-Y (Box 1714-1719)
  - Z (Box 1719-1723)
- Refugee case files (mainly Eastern European)
  - A-Kl (Box 1661-1666)
  - J-Kel (Box 1025-1029)
  - Ken-Kot (Box 1015-1019)
  - Kou-Lesch (Box 1044-1048)
  - Lesz-Mar (Box 1063-1069)
  - Mat-N (Box 1077-1082)
  - Mi-Par (Box 1072-1077)
  - Pas-Py (Box 1087-1092)
  - Q-Sej (Box 1039-1043)
  - Sel-Sz (Box 1020-1025)
  - R-Z (Box 1656-1661)
- Refugee case files through 1983
  - A-An (Box 1908-1913)
  - Ab-Beri (Box 2030-2034)
  - Ak-Al (Box 2010)
  - Bern-Dumitri (Box 2249-2254)
  - Dumitru-Har (Box 2325-2329)
  - Har-Hov (Box 2010)
  - I-J (Box 2280-2284)
  - Kesa-Kesh (Box 2011)
  - Kes-Kod (Box 2206-2210)
  - Kog-Krk (Box 1914-1918)
  - Kro-Les (Box 1929-1933)
  - Leu-Malc (Box 1949-1953)
  - Male-Mase (Box 2276-2279)
  - Mash-Miko (Box 2266-2270)
  - Miku-Mor (Box 2320-2324)
  - Mos-Naz (Box 1954-1958)
  - Naz-Nor (Box 2045-2049)
  - Nou-Pal (Box 2040-2044)
  - Pam-Pj (Box 2020-2024)
  - Pe-Sah (Box 2055-2059)
  - Pl-Pul (Box 2384-2388)
  - Pur-Riv (Box 2217-2221)
  - Sai-Tab (Box 2036-2039)
  - Ser-Simo (Box 2065-2069)
  - Simp-Stam (Box 2373-2377)
  - Stam-Su (Box 1999-2003)
  - Tan-Til (Box 2305-2309)
  - Tim-Tur (Box 2080-2084)
  - Tus-Vin (Box 2368-2372)
  - Vir-Wis (Box 2310-2314)
  - Wit-Yes (Box 2075-2079)
  - Yev-Zd (Box 2315-2319)
  - Ze-Zw (Box 2012-2014)
- Refugee case files, 1984
  - A-Bah (Box 2362-2367)
  - Baj-Bo (Box 2346-2347)
  - Bay-Far (Box 2211-2216)
  - Far-Gol (Box 2004-2007)
  - Gol-Hoss (Box 2348-2350)
  - Hoss-Kr (Box 2085-2088)
  - Io-Mal (Box 2070-2074)
  - Mam-Mem (Box 2008-2009)
  - Men-Mirs (Box 2089)
  - Mirz-Mu (Box 2330-2331)
  - N-Piech (Box 2335-2339)
  - Piecz-Ras (Box 2332-2334)
  - Ras-Sol (Box 1897-1902)
  - Sol-Stark (Box 2340)
  - Starz-Vor (Box 2394-2399)
  - Vor-Z (Box 2201-2203)
- Refugee case files, 1985
  - A-Di (Box 2351-2355)
  - Dj-Jed (Box 2060-2064)
  - Jel-Mot (Box 2255-2260)
  - Mos-Sic (Box 2341-2345)
  - Sie-Z (Box 1881-1885)
- Refugee case files, 1986
  - A-C (Box 1876-1880)
  - D-H (Box 2095-2099)
  - I-Men (Box 2129-2133)
  - Mes-R (Box 2150-2154)
  - S-Z (Box 2139-2144)
- Refugee case files, 1987
  - A-Ch (Box 2170-2174)
  - Ci-Haj (Box 2134-2138)
  - Hak-L (Box 2155-2159)
  - M-Po (Box 2115-2119)
  - Pr-T (Box 2110-2114)
- Refugee case files, 1988
  - A-Bar (Box 1871-1875)
  - Bar-Del (Box 2300-2304)
  - Del-Guk (Box 1987-1991)
  - Gul-Khu (Box 2100-2104)
  - Khu-Meh (Box 1992-1996)
  - Meh-Ova (Box 2120-2124)
  - Ova-Sar (Box 2160-2164)
  - Sar-Tj (Box 2175-2179)
  - To-Z (Box 2125-2128)
- Refugee case files, 1989
  - A-Bor (Box 2291-2295)
  - Bor-Fod (Box 2105-2109)
  - Fod-Jac (Box 2180-2184)
  - G-K (Box 2035)
  - Jaf-Luk (Box 2165-2169)
  - Lup-Oga (Box 2090-2094)
  - Ogb-Sef (Box 2185-2189)
  - Say-To (Box 2145-2149)
  - Tr-Z (Box 2296-2299)
- Cuban refugee case files
  - A-Alvarez N (Box 207-211)
  - Alvarez O-Bas (Box 202-206)
  - Bat-Cabo (Box 198-202)
  - Cabr-Castillo L (Box 211-215)
  - Castillo M-Cuer (Box 791-795)
  - Cues-Diaz G (Box 795-800)
  - Diaz H-Fem (Box 800-804)
  - Fer-Fon (Box 805-809)
  - For-Garcia R (Box 828-832)
  - Garcia S-Gonzalez Man (Box 832-837)
  - Gonzalez Mar-Hernandez D (Box 837-842)
  - Hernandez E-Lam (Box 842-847)
  - Lan-Lop (Box 1155-1160)
  - Lor-Martinez Ri (Box 1160-1165)
  - Martinez Ro-Montes (Box 1165-1170)
  - Montesi-Os (Box 1170-1175)
  - Ot-Perez L (Box 1120-1124)
  - Perez M-Rad (Box 1124-1130)
  - Ram-Rodriguez C (Box 1130-1134)
  - Rodriguez D-Roma (Box 1135-1139)
  - Rome-Sanc (Box 862-866)
  - Sand-Tap (Box 866-871)
  - Tar-Var (Box 871-875)
  - Vaz-Z (Box 876-879)
- Cuban refugee case files, 1980-1981
  - A-Alvarez (Box 1997-1998)
  - Alvarez-B (Box 2204-2205)
  - F-G (Box 2192-2195)
  - H-K (Box 2190-2191)
  - M-Perez S (Box 1034-1038)
  - Perez L-Sn (Box 1106-1110)
  - So-Z (Box 1092-1095)
- Cuban refugee case files, by country (Box 1053-1058)
- Chilean and Argentine refugee case files (Box 1244-1249)
- Chilean refugee case files
  - A-Si (Box 521-525)
  - So-Z (Box 526-530)
- Ugandan refugee case files
  - A-L (Box 526-530)
  - M-Z (Box 530-535)
- Chinese refugee case files
  - A-Cheuk, miscellaneous (Box 1263-1267)
  - Cheun-Ho J (Box 1267-1272)
  - Ho K-Lam (Box 1272-1276)
  - Lau-Li (Box 1277-1281)
  - Lia-Po (Box 1249-1254)
  - Pu-Wai (Box 1254-1258)
  - Wan-Y (Box 1258-1263)
- Indochinese refugee case files
  - A-Cao T (Box 1738-1744)
  - Cao V-Dang Ngoc Ba (Box 1744-1750)
  - Dang Ngoc Bi-Dinh Man (Box 1750-1756)
  - Dinh Mao-Doa (Box 1756-1762)
  - Don-Ho Q (Box 463-468)
  - Ho P-Huye (Box 468-474)
  - Huyn-Ka (Box 474-479)
  - Ke-Le Huu D (Box 479-484)
  - Le Huu H-Le Ti (Box 682-687)
  - Le Tr-Luon (Box 688-693)
  - Luong-Mai N (Box 693-698)
  - Mai T-Nguyen A (Box 699-704)
  - Nguyen B-Nguyen Duc C (Box 157-162)
  - Nguyen Duc D-Nguyen Huy D (Box 162-167)
  - Nguyen Huy H-Nguyen Ngoc M (Box 168-173)
  - Nguyen Ngoc N-Nguyen Thanh D (Box 173-178)
  - Nguyen Thanh G-Nguyen Thi H (Box 561-566)
  - Nguyen Thi K-Nguyen Thi Xi (Box 566-571)
  - Nguyen Thi Xu-Nguyen Van Duc (Box 572-577)
  - Nguyen Van Dun-Nguyen Van Tan (Box 577-582)
  - Nguyen Van Tanh-Pa (Box 1303-1308)
  - Pham A-Pham Thi Ha (Box 1308-1313)
  - Pham Thi Ho-Phan Huu Na (Box 1314-1319)
  - Phan Huu Ng-Phung T (Box 1319-1324)
  - Phung V-Than (Box 1281-1286)
  - Thanh-Tran Duc H (Box 1287-1292)
  - Tran Duc T-Tran Phuc (Box 1292-1297)
  - Tran Phuo-Tran Thi Toa (Box 1298-1303)
  - Tran Thi Tot-Tran Van Tro (Box 1829-1834)
  - Tran Van Tru-Truong Thi Mo (Box 1834-1839)
  - Truong Thi My-Vo Van A (Box 1839-1845)
  - Vo Van B-Vu (Box 1845-1850)
- Indochinese refugee case files
  - A-Boun (Box 1532-1537)
  - Boup-Cha (Box 1537-1541)
  - Chac-Chas (Box 1541-1546)
  - Chau-Chh (Box 1214-1218)
  - Chi-Dang B (Box 1219-1223)
  - Dang C-De (Box 1224-1228)
  - Di-Do Van D (Box 1228-1232)
  - Do Van H-Duong Thi (Box 1563-1568)
  - Duong Thu-Hang Q (Box 1569-1574)
  - Hang S-Hoang Quoc B (Box 1574-1579)
  - Hoang Quoc V-Huynh Huu Hiep (Box 1580-1585)
  - Huynh Huu Hieu-Huynh Van Tan (Box 976-981)
  - Huynh Van Tao-Keomanni (Box 981-986)
  - Keomanny-Khounn (Box 987-992)
  - Khounp-Lal (Box 1345-1350)
  - Lam-Lau (Box 1351-1356)
  - Lav-Le Thi To (Box 1356-1361)
  - Le Thi Tr-Lim N (Box 1362-1367)
  - Lim P-Luong Ngo (Box 639-644)
  - Luong Ngu-Ly Lam (Box 645-650)
  - Ly Lan-Mai T (Box 650-656)
  - Mai V-Mo (Box 656-661)
  - Mu-Ngo Ti (Box 617-622)
  - Ngo To-Nguyen Hoang Q (Box 622-628)
  - Nguyen Hoang T-Nguyen Ng (Box 628-633)
  - Nguyen Nh-Nguyen Thi D (Box 634-639)
  - Nguyen Thi G-Nguyen To (Box 1324-1329)
  - Nguyen Tr-Nguyen Van Li (Box 1330-1335)
  - Nguyen Van Lo-Nguyen Viet Q (Box 1335-1340)
  - Nguyen Viet T-Oud (Box 1340-1345)
  - Ouk-Pham Ngoc H (Box 597-601)
  - Pham Ngoc K-Phan Ngoc L (Box 601-606)
  - Phan Ngoc M-Phetsam (Box 607-612)
  - Phetsar-Phout (Box 612-617)
  - Phouth-Quach P (Box 136-141)
  - Quach Q-Saecha (Box 141-146)
  - Saechu-Saw (Box 147-152)
  - Say-Sihavong, K (Box 152-157)
  - Sihavong, S-Son (Box 1426-1432)
  - Sop-Sy (Box 1432-1437)
  - Sya-Tat B (Box 1437-1443)
  - Tat C-Tha (Box 1443-1448)
  - The-Tong P (Box 770-775)
  - Tong S-Tram Kim Q (Box 775-780)
  - Tran Kim S-Tran Thi C (Box 780-786)
  - Tran Thi D-Tran Van M (Box 786-791)
  - Tran Van N-Tro (Box 1449-1454)
  - Tru-Tu T (Box 1454-1460)
  - Tu V-Vann (Box 1460-1466)
  - Vanp-Vone (Box 1466-1471)
  - Vong-Vu The (Box 1411-1416)
  - Vu Thi-Xayp (Box 1416-1421)
  - Xays-Y (Box 1421-1426)
- Indochinese refugee case files
  - A-H (Box 1590-1595)
  - I-M (Box 1596-1601)
  - N-Pham (Box 1601-1605)
  - Phan-To (Box 421-426)
  - Tr-Z (Box 426-431)
- Indochinese refugee case files
  - A-C, miscellaneous (Box 1762-1767)
  - D-S (Box 1767-1772)
  - T-Y (Box 1772-1778)
- Indochinese refugee case files
  - A-Hua (Box 1772-1778)
  - Huy-Q (Box 1778-1784)
  - S-Y, miscellaneous (Box 1585-1589)
- Indochinese refugee case files
  - A-Nguyen T (Box 1859-1865)
  - Nguyen V-Y, miscellaneous (Box 1865-1870)
- Indochinese refugee case files
  - A-Die (Box 1083-1087)
  - Din-Hon (Box 1011-1015)
  - Hoa-Khi (Box 1048-1053)
  - Kho-La (Box 1029-1034)
  - Le-Luu L (Box 583-587)
  - Luu Q-Ngi (Box 1058-1063)
  - Ngo-Nguyen Van Ng (Box 1111-1115)
  - Nguyen Van Nh-Pho (Box 593-596)
  - Phok-S (Box 588-592)
  - T-Tran Pho (Box 1101-1106)
  - Tran Phu-Ung C (Box 1096-1100)
  - Ung K-Y (Box 1069-1072)
- Indochinese refugee case files
  - B-H (Box 1850-1853)
  - K-V (Box 1853-1858)
- Indochinese refugee case files, 1982 October-December (Box 1934-1936)
- Indochinese refugee case files, 1983
  - A-D (Box 1937-1938)
  - E-Nguyen H (Box 2261-2265)
  - Nguyen K-Sil (Box 1965-1969)
  - Sim-Y (Box 2271-2274)
- Indochinese refugee case files, 1984
  - A-Che (Box 2275)
  - Chh-Le Tha (Box 1939-1943)
  - Le Thi-Nguyen Thi Ti (Box 1919-1923)
  - Nguyen Thi Tu-Thl (Box 2238-2243)
  - Tho-Y (Box 1891-1894)
- Indochinese refugee case files, 1985
  - A-Do Va (Box 1895-1896)
  - Do Vi-M (Box 1959-1964)
  - N-Phom (Box 2233-2237)
  - Phon-Y (Box 1975-1982)
- Indochinese refugee case files, 1986
  - A-Lo (Box 1886-1890)
  - Lu-Pham Van H (Box 2222-2226)
  - Pham Van N-Truong Thi D (Box 1903-1907)
  - Truong Thi E-Z (Box 2285-2286)
- Indochinese refugee case files, 1987
  - A-La (Box 2287-2290)
  - Le-Phan (Box 2356-2361)
  - Phang-Vo T (Box 2050-2054)
  - Vo V-Y (Box 2025)
- Indochinese refugee case files, 1988
  - A-Huynh The (Box 2026-2029)
  - Huynh Thi-L (Box 1944-1948)
  - N-Pham Th (Box 2389-2393)
  - Pham Tr-Thi (Box 1924-1928)
  - Tho-Y (Box 1970-1974)
- Indochinese refugee case files, 1989
  - A-Hua (Box 2015-2019)
  - Huy-M (Box 2196-2200)
  - N-Nguyen Van C (Box 2244-2248)
  - Nguyen Van S-Thai P (Box 2227-2232)
  - Thai T-V (Box 2378-2383)
- Office of Immigration Indochinese refugee case files
  - A-L (Box 431-437)
  - M-P (Box 437-441)
  - Q-Y (Box 1527-1531)
- Refugee case files by country
  - Miscellaneous (Box 530-540)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1505-1510)
  - Miscellaneous, Flight schedules, 1977 (Box 1523-1526)
  - Australia (Box 1492-1497)
  - Canada
    - A-Ch (Box 730-734)
    - Ci-G (Box 734-739)
    - H-Kr (Box 739-744)
    - Ku-Ne (Box 745-749)
    - Ng-Sc (Box 1510-1514)
    - Se-U (Box 1515-1519)
    - V-Z (Box 1519-1523)
  - Great Britain
  - Afghanistan-Bulgaria (Box 1497-1501)
  - Chile-Zaire (Box 1502-1505)
- Closed cases, C-Q (Box 1983-1986)
- Incremental Materials (Box 2400-3802)